[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Juliet 'i melt with you' was which band's signature hit released on their 'after the snow' album in 1982",
    "Answer": "Modern english"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "Honolulu\" means _____________",
    "Answer": "Sheltered harbor"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "How many gallons of fuel does a jumbo jet use during take off?",
    "Answer": "Four thousand"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "In the game of cricket which bird name means scoring no runs",
    "Answer": "Duck"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "With which singer did Westlife record a version of Against all Odds in 2000?",
    "Answer": "Mariah Carey"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "In 1951 Howard Hawks Produced The Thing. Who Directed The 1982 remake, Starring Kurt Russell",
    "Answer": "John Carpenter"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The Paris stock exchange",
    "Answer": "Bourse"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "What amendment to the u.s. constitution ended prohibition",
    "Answer": "The twenty first"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What game of chance was originally called 'Beano'",
    "Answer": "Bingo"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "Where Did Napoleon Bonaparte Die In Exile?",
    "Answer": "St Helena"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "The eggs of this sturgeon are the preferred form of caviar.",
    "Answer": "Beluga"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the motto of the three muskateers",
    "Answer": "All for one & one for all"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the flower that stands for: a heart ignorant of love",
    "Answer": "White rosebud"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What nationality was the sculpture Brancusi",
    "Answer": "Romanian"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "Category": "Toys & Games",
    "Question": "Charles Darrow based his game upon the 1904 \"The Landlord's Game\".",
    "Answer": "Monopoly"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who sang \"I Want My MTV\" on the Dire Straits song \"Money For Nothing\"?",
    "Answer": "Sting"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "What country did poinsettias originally come from? (Mexico,Us, Spain ,Brazil)",
    "Answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Who Starred As Cole Porter In The 1945 Film Night & Day",
    "Answer": "Cary Grant"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Before Hitting The Big Time As A Singer & Tv Personality What Was \"Perry Como's \" Profession",
    "Answer": "A Barber / Hair Dresser"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "What was finally a top ten hit for Ce Ce Peniston on its 1992 Re-Release",
    "Answer": "Finally"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Seventeen thousand how many camels carried the 117,000 volumes of abdul kassem ismael's library",
    "Answer": 400
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Under Michigan State law who are officially classed mechanics",
    "Answer": "Dentists"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Medieval monks invented this stopper, necessary for champagne",
    "Answer": "Cork"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In the body luteinizing hormone is produced by what gland",
    "Answer": "Pituitary"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "What colour is chablis?",
    "Answer": "White"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "Football: The Denver ____?",
    "Answer": "Broncos"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What are the stars in traditional Cornish Star Gazey pie",
    "Answer": "Pilchards eyes"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is raku",
    "Answer": "Japanese pottery"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Proverbially it was a bold man who  first ate what",
    "Answer": "An Oyster"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "Where is the oldest distillery in the world?",
    "Answer": "The Old Bushmills, Cty Antrim"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What countries days include Fire day, Water day and wood day",
    "Answer": "Japan Tue Wed Thu"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In golf what would you put in your shag bag",
    "Answer": "Practice Balls"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Constance Markiewicz, Became The Worlds First Ever What In 1918?",
    "Answer": "First British Female MP"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "Which Modern Gymnastics Event Made Its First Appearance At The 2000 Sydney Olympics",
    "Answer": "Trampolining"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Burning potassium has what colour flame",
    "Answer": "Purple"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who directed the monochrome (sepia) sequences at the beginning and end of \"the wizard of oz\" (1939)",
    "Answer": "King vidor"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "Who Became premier of Cuba in 1959.",
    "Answer": "Fidel Castro"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "According to the song what did my true love give to me on the fifth day of Christmas",
    "Answer": "Five Gold Rings"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the cap on the fire hydrant called",
    "Answer": "Bonnet"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "What is the capital of Philippines ?",
    "Answer": "Manila"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "Who Originated The Uncertainty Principle",
    "Answer": "Heisenberg"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What dodgers and cubs first-baseman dropped baseball to take up actin",
    "Answer": "Chuck"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which usical instrument was invented by Henry Schluter?",
    "Answer": "Vibraphone"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "How long is a silver anniversary",
    "Answer": "25 years"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Johnny Marr Teamed Up With Which Former New Order Member To Form The Band Electronic",
    "Answer": "Bernard Sumner"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Test of metal or ore for ingredients and quality",
    "Answer": "Assay"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is a woolly bear",
    "Answer": "Caterpillar"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the name of the telescope that was placed in orbit in the eighties?",
    "Answer": "Hubble"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Where was The Beast, the first mobile robot, developed",
    "Answer": "Johns hopkins"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The province of Alberta in Canada has been completely free of rats since what year",
    "Answer": 1905
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Arlanda is the airport which serves which European city",
    "Answer": "Stockholm"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "What Group Did Nick Cave Sing With Before Forming The Bad Seeds",
    "Answer": "The Birthday Party"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "Sound Navigation Ranging is better known as _________.",
    "Answer": "Sonar"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is a group of geese called",
    "Answer": "Gaggle"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Which Music Festival Was Attended By Over 400,000 People In 1969",
    "Answer": "Woodstock"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The last Nascar driver to serve jail time for running moonshine was who",
    "Answer": "Buddy arrington"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which Capital City Is Home To \"Carrasco\" International Airport",
    "Answer": "Montevideo (Uruguay)"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The worlds what museum is at 19 Green belt North York Ontario",
    "Answer": "Contraceptive"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia the fear of?",
    "Answer": "Long words"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "Category": "Toys & Games",
    "Question": "In the game of chess, which piece has the most freedom to move?",
    "Answer": "Queen"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "What Is The Function Of The Thyroid Gland",
    "Answer": "To Regulate Growth & The Metabolism"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Who Claimed That \"Mama Gave Birth To The Soul Children",
    "Answer": "Queen Latifah"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "Singapore banned which popular western foodstuff because of litter implicatons?",
    "Answer": "Chewing Guim"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Metal framework on a vehicle to protect it in the event of a collision with a large animal",
    "Answer": "Bull bar"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is a Bellwether",
    "Answer": "Leader of flock of sheep"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "As what is 'South West Township' known in south africa",
    "Answer": "Soweto"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the most important mineral for strong bones & teeth",
    "Answer": "Calcium"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "What asian leader was known as the little brown saint",
    "Answer": "Mahatma gandhi"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Of who did the u.s postal service print 500 million stamps in 1993",
    "Answer": "Elvis"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is 'bountiful mother' in latin",
    "Answer": "Alma mater"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What was the name of john lennon and cynthia lennon's son",
    "Answer": "Sean"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Lake Vanern is the largest lake in which country",
    "Answer": "Sweden"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the missing word in english with the letter combination 'uu' vacuum, muumuu, continuum, residuum, duumvir",
    "Answer": "Duumvirate"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "Who was the ruler of the USSR from 1917-22?",
    "Answer": "Vladimir Lenin"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Isolophobia is the fear of",
    "Answer": "Solitude, being alone"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "What Did Jesse Reno Invent Using Traditional Conveyor Belt Principles To Pull Folding Steps Up A Slope",
    "Answer": "The Escalator"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Name the wife of King Ahab, who Jehu ordered to be thrown to her death from a window",
    "Answer": "Jezebel"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "If not Shakespeare what links Juliet Cleopatra Mark Antony",
    "Answer": "Commit Suicide"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who was the first person to prove that planets move in elliptical orbits",
    "Answer": "Kepler"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who was the first black mayor of Chicago?",
    "Answer": "Harold Washington"
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "Who Won The US Open Men's *Tennis * Title in 1990 At The Age Of Just 19?",
    "Answer": "Pete Sampras"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which architect designed London's tallest building The Shard?",
    "Answer": "Renzo Piano"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which meteorological phenomena means \"a curl of hair\" in Latin",
    "Answer": "Cirrus - clouds"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Originally a Toss Pot did a lot of what",
    "Answer": "Drinking - Alcohol"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What country is Men Without Hats originally from?",
    "Answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "What group was Ringo with before the Beatles?",
    "Answer": "Rory Storm and the Hurricanes"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What Did Bruce Willis, Harvey Keitel & Winston Churchill All have to overcome?",
    "Answer": "Stutters / Stammers"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What 3 ingredients make a sidecar cocktail",
    "Answer": "Brandy Cointreau Lemon juice"
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Anna Maria Louisa Italiano changed her name to what",
    "Answer": "Anne Bancroft"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "An Aficionado originally followed what sport",
    "Answer": "Bullfighting"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "Category": "People & Places",
    "Question": "Which is the largest of the Canary Islands?",
    "Answer": "Tenerife"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "The land that would eventually be known as oklahoma was part of the what in 1803",
    "Answer": "Louisiana purchase."
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which U.S. boxer was known as 'The Manessa Mauler'",
    "Answer": "Jack dempsey"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Who Had Minor Hits With \"Dogs Of Lust\", \"Slow Emotion Replay\" And \"Dis -Infected\" EP",
    "Answer": "The The"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What does a Stupprator prefer sexually",
    "Answer": "Virgins"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "An elephant has 400000 what in its trunk",
    "Answer": "Muscles"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The Zagros mountain range is in which country",
    "Answer": "Iran"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "What is the highest mountain in the Appalachian range?",
    "Answer": "Mt. Mitchell"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In South Korea traffic police must report what",
    "Answer": "Tourists bribes taken"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What does SALT stand for",
    "Answer": "Strategic arms limitation treaty"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which chemical element has the atomic number 4?",
    "Answer": "Berylium"
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who had a hit no 5 in US 1971 with Bridge over Troubled Water",
    "Answer": "Aretha Franklin"
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "William the First was crowned on Christmas day, but in what year",
    "Answer": "1066"
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What country covers an entire continent",
    "Answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "In which film did Donna Summer make her debut as an aspiring disco singer?",
    "Answer": "Thank God It's Friday"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who was responsible for driving the english out of scotland in 1297",
    "Answer": "William"
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Which duo released albums called Introspective and Very?",
    "Answer": "Pet Shop Boys"
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the front of a saddle called?",
    "Answer": "Pommel"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Fried Chicken Strawberry Shortcake trad Xmas eve meal where",
    "Answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "U.S. Captials - Michigan",
    "Answer": "Lansing"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which epic film was based on a novel by Lew Wallace",
    "Answer": "Ben hur"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What are the young of a rabbit called",
    "Answer": "Kittens"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Paul wrote \"Martha My Dear\". Who did he know who was named Martha?",
    "Answer": "His Dog"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Who filled in for Ringo on the Beatles' 1964 world tour?",
    "Answer": "Jimmy Nicol"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What planet did Alf come from?",
    "Answer": "Melmac"
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who wrote dionne warwick's 'walk on by' and 'say a little prayer'",
    "Answer": "Burt"
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the technical difference between rowing and sculling",
    "Answer": "Rowing means using a single oar"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Outside poland, where is the largest polish population",
    "Answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In The Film Saving Private Ryan What Was Private Ryan's First Name?",
    "Answer": "James"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What song won the grammy for \"song of the year\" in 1977",
    "Answer": "You light up my"
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Which Band From Manchester Incluides The Former Entertainments Manager From The Hacienda (Nightclub)",
    "Answer": "M People"
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "How did George II die",
    "Answer": "Fell off toilet"
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Electric, Perse and smalt shades of which colour",
    "Answer": "Blue"
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Every day in the US people steal $20000 from where",
    "Answer": "Vending machines"
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who wrote \"The Picture of Dorian Grey",
    "Answer": "Oscar wilde"
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Indiana jones: who was known to get lost in his own museum",
    "Answer": "Marcus brody"
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In Which Childrens TV Show Will You Find The Characters Of \"Florrie & Baby Pom",
    "Answer": "The Fimbles"
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Mr Chips said goodbye from Brookfield school - What subject",
    "Answer": "Latin"
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Where is the worlds largest mine",
    "Answer": "Carletonville South Africa"
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Florence Nightingale tended the soldiers in which war",
    "Answer": "Crimean"
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the name of the cord joining a mother & her unborn child",
    "Answer": "Umbilical cord"
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What Is Joseph Cyril Bamfords Claim To Fame?",
    "Answer": "The JCB Earth Mover"
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "Category": "Language",
    "Question": "The name for this semi-precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water",
    "Answer": "Aquamarine"
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "What Name Appears In The Title Of Both A Beatles Hit And A Novel By ThomasHardy?",
    "Answer": "Jude"
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "An atom is comprized of these 3 subatomic particles: electron, neutron, & _____",
    "Answer": "Proton"
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Which Group Comprises Of Colin Angus And Mr C",
    "Answer": "The Shamen"
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What are the colours of the Olympics rings (in order).?",
    "Answer": "Blue Yellow Black Green Red"
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Who Was The First Woman To Appear Naked On The Front Cover Of The Radio Times",
    "Answer": "Helen Mirren"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What was known as the spice island",
    "Answer": "Zanzibar"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In which county is Charnwood Forest",
    "Answer": "Leicestershire"
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the name of the Tokyo Stock Market Index",
    "Answer": "Nikkei"
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In The Pilgrim's Progress, which city of Christian's final destination",
    "Answer": "Celestial city"
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "What Do You Get If A Male Donkey Breeds With A Horse?",
    "Answer": "A Mule"
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "How Many Suits Are There In A Game Of (Mah Jong)",
    "Answer": "3 Suits"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "Category": "Food & Drink",
    "Question": "Who released the following album 'Strange brew '",
    "Answer": "Cream"
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the derivative of sin x",
    "Answer": "Cos x"
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What name is given to the fraction part of a logarithm number?",
    "Answer": "Mantissa"
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Ralph Freeman designed which Australian landmark",
    "Answer": "Sydney harbour bridge"
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "In Wonderland, Who Took A Watch Out Of His Waistcoat Pocket Only To Discover That He Was Late",
    "Answer": "The White Rabbit"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What animals teeth were used as knife blades by the Indians",
    "Answer": "Beaver"
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "In The Film 'Halloween' For How Many Years Was The Killer Locked Up In An Asylum Before He Escaped",
    "Answer": "15 Years"
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Norman Bean became famous as which author",
    "Answer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs"
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In which tv series does fred savage play kevin arnold",
    "Answer": "The wonder years"
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "The valuable blue form of corundum is called:",
    "Answer": "Sapphire"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "It takes approximately 69,000 venom extractions from the __________",
    "Answer": "To fill a 1_pint container. coral snake"
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What are people encouraged to kiss under",
    "Answer": "Mistletoe"
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In Islington in London its a 50 fine for sleeping where",
    "Answer": "The Public Library"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "If a dish is served pomontier what does it contain",
    "Answer": "Potatoes"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "What Describes A Person With No Skin Pigment",
    "Answer": "An Albino"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Which Of These People Is The Shortest \"Jarvis Cocker, Micheal Stipe Or Nicky Wire",
    "Answer": "Michael Stipe"
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Creedence clearwater revival sings 'have you ever ______'",
    "Answer": "Seen the rain"
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In the tv series 'leave it to beaver', what was wally's best friend's name",
    "Answer": "Eddie haskell"
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "In Boxing Who Suffered Defeats To Tim Witherspoon, Mike Tyson & Lennox Lewis",
    "Answer": "Frank Bruno"
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "In 'Bridget Jones Diary'', Bridget Jones makes a New Years Resolution, to sort out her life, meet a man and keep a diary, but who played Bridget Jones",
    "Answer": "Rene Zellweger"
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What fashion designers symbol is a swan",
    "Answer": "Gloria Vanderbilt"
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In which English town or city would you find The Christmas Steps",
    "Answer": "Bristol"
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "On which river is Rome located",
    "Answer": "Tiber"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "96% of American children can recognise - who",
    "Answer": "Ronald MacDonald"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "The female American Oyster lays an average of 500 million eggs per year. Usually only one oyster out of the bunch reaches __________",
    "Answer": "Maturity"
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What are the grinding teeth called",
    "Answer": "Molars"
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "Category": "Science & Nature",
    "Question": "A one-humped camel is called a _________.",
    "Answer": "Dromedary"
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In 2001 one active UK warship named after an Englishman who",
    "Answer": "Sir Winston Churchill"
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What country has the most bookshops per head population",
    "Answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "Which U.S. state has the least rainfall",
    "Answer": "Nevada"
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "Category": "Music",
    "Question": "Who Sang The Smokin Dance Hit \"Feel It\" Including The Featured Artist",
    "Answer": "Tamperer Feat Maya (Pepper)"
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Legal Terms: A supplement to a will.",
    "Answer": "Codicil"
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Edward Whymper was the first to do what",
    "Answer": "Climb Matterhorn"
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "A 1957 title recorded by the Crickets, was a line taken from the classic John Ford Western's 'The Searchers'. What was the title",
    "Answer": "That'll Be the Day"
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Opperman what is the capital of iowa",
    "Answer": "Des moines"
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Saanen, Hongtong & Toggenburg Are All Breeds Of Which Animal",
    "Answer": "Goats"
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which 9-fingered pop pianist starred in the film Its all Happening",
    "Answer": "Russ"
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "Category": "Sports & Leisure",
    "Question": "A Silver Fern Is The Emblem Of Which Nations Rugby Union Team?",
    "Answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the Latin word for liquid produced by the Ficus Elastica",
    "Answer": "Latex"
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the fear of parents-in-law known as",
    "Answer": "Soceraphobia"
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which is the only work by Dukas most people have ever heard of",
    "Answer": "The sorcerer's apprentice"
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "Category": "Geography",
    "Question": "What queen were the virgin islands named for in 1627",
    "Answer": "Elizabeth i"
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What did henry shrapnel invent",
    "Answer": "Exploding shell"
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What's the collective noun for a group of gulls",
    "Answer": "Colony"
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "The American Society for Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (aspca) was formed in what year",
    "Answer": 1866
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In Pac Man eating what was worth 5000 points",
    "Answer": "Banana"
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "Category": "History & Holidays",
    "Question": "What Did My True Love Give To Me On The \"\"Nineth\"\" Day Of Christmas\"",
    "Answer": "9 Ladies Dancing"
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the Capital of: Virgin Islands",
    "Answer": "Charlotte amalie"
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What does Do Loop do for a living",
    "Answer": "Computer programmer"
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "Category": "People & Places",
    "Question": "What Did You Associate With Rod Hull ?",
    "Answer": "Emu"
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which famous Englishwoman was born in Florence on 12th May 1820,where her well-to-do parents were temporarily resident",
    "Answer": "Florence nightingale"
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "What is the opposite of nocturnal",
    "Answer": "Diurnal"
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Which Saint is said to have carried his own head for six miles after his death?",
    "Answer": "St Denis"
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "Five out of six of the Village people have got what",
    "Answer": "Moustaches"
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "Category": "General",
    "Question": "In Watership Down rabbit language what is a hrududu",
    "Answer": "A motor car"
  }
]